<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BookCart</string>
    <string name="reg">Here\'s your first step with us!</string>
    <string name="Open">Open navigation</string>
    <string name="Close">Close navigation</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="title_activity_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="hp_first">It is a story about Harry Potter,
        an orphan brought up by his aunt and uncle because his parents were killed when he was a baby.
        Harry is unloved by his uncle and aunt but everything changes when he is invited to join Hogwarts School of
        Witchcraft and Wizardry and he finds out he is  a wizard.</string>

    <string name="hp_second">The plot follows Harry second year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry,
        during which a series of messages on the walls of the school corridors warn that the
        "Chamber of Secrets" has been opened and that the "heir of Slytherin" would kill all pupils who do not come
        from all-magical families.
</string>

    <string name="hp_third">The book follows Harry Potter,
        a young wizard, in his third year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.
        Along with friends Ronald Weasley and Hermione Granger, Harry investigates Sirius Black,
        an escaped prisoner from Azkaban, the wizard prison, believed to be one of Lord Voldemort old allies.
</string>
    <string name="hp_four">Synopsis. Harry, Ron and Hermione enter their fourth year at Hogwarts.
        After having a strange dream of the Dark Lord and his Death Eaters,
        Harry Potter awakes at the Weasleys house where they shortly depart for the 422nd Quidditch World Cup.
        After the match, the camp is attacked by Death Eaters.</string>

    <string name="hp_five">It follows Harry Potter struggles through his fifth year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft
        and Wizardry, including the surreptitious return of the antagonist Lord Voldemort,
        O.W.L. exams, and an obstructive Ministry of Magic.</string>
    <string name="hp_six">In this book, Harry Potter learns a lot about Lord Voldemort past,
        and Harry Potter prepares for the final battle against his nemesis with the help of Headmaster Dumbledore.
        But in that time, Voldemort returns to power, and makes a plan to destroy Harry.</string>
    <string name="hp_seven">The Deathly Hallows is about Harry Potter and his friends finding ways to destroy Voldemort.
        They learn that even good contains a bit of evil, and vise versa.
        Even though the trio faces many difficulties, they persevere.</string>
    <string name="hp_eigth">“Harry Potter and the Cursed Child” is about the journey Albus takes while growing up,
        and the roles he and his best friend, Scorpius (Draco Malfoy son),
        play when dark forces, perhaps in league with Voldemort,
        once again threaten the fate of the planet</string>
    <string name="book">The Shiva Purana is one of eighteen major texts of the Purana genre of Sanskrit texts in Hinduism,
        and part of the Shaivism literature corpus.It primarily revolves around the Hindu god Shiva and goddess Parvati,
        but references and reveres all gods.</string>
    <string name="book_one">Seven Secrets of Shiva is a concise book
        about Lord Shiva and the stories and metaphors related to him.
        It also contains tales related to his family,
        i.e., Goddess Shakti, Lord Ganesha, and Kartikeya.
        Seven Secrets of Shiva by Devdutt Pattanaik.
        The language of the book is easy to read.</string>

    <string name="book_two">Death; An Inside Story is a book that explores the topic of death and the afterlife uniquely.
        The book is written in a style that encourages you to entertain the possibility of an existential reality
        beyond the limited realm of logic and intellect.
        It encourages you to explore it with an open mind and not decide between true and false
        when it comes to something that is not in our experience.

        The book elaborates on practical preparations one can make for one’s death,
        how best we can assist someone who is dying,
        and how we can continue to support their journey even after they have passed away. </string>

    <string name="book_third">Inner Engineering is your personalized tool for joy and wellbeing.
        As Sadhguru explains in the introduction, “My aim in this book is to help make joy your constant companion.
        To make that happen, this book offers you not a sermon, but a science; not a teaching,
        but a technology; not a precept, but a path. It is now time to start exploring that science,
        working the technology, walking the path.”</string>

    <string name="book_four">J.K. Rowling’s five-film Fantastic Beasts adventure series
        continues with the original screenplay for Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes of Grindelwald
       At the end of Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them,
        the powerful Dark wizard Gellert Grindelwald was captured in New York with the help of Newt Scamander.
        But, making good on his threat, Grindelwald escapes custody and sets about gathering followers,
        most unsuspecting of his true agenda: to raise pure-blood wizards up to rule over all non-magical beings.
        In an effort to thwart Grindelwald’s plans, Albus Dumbledore enlists Newt, his former Hogwarts student,
        who agrees to help once again, unaware of the dangers that lie ahead. Lines are drawn as love and loyalty are tested,
        even among the truest friends and family, in an increasingly divided wizarding world.
        This second original screenplay from J.K. Rowling, illustrated with stunning line art from MinaLima,
        expands on earlier events that helped shape the wizarding world, with some surprising nods to the Harry Potter
        stories that will delight fans of both the books and films.</string>
    <string name="book_five">Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them (often referred to as simply Fantastic Beasts)
        is a 2001 guide book written by British author J. K. Rowling
        (under the pen name of the fictitious author Newt Scamander)
        about the magical creatures in the Harry Potter universe.</string>

</resources>